Happy birthday!
Hey! Cheers! Thank you, guys!
Alright!
Babe, you’re not drinking.
Come on, drink!
Go, go, go!
More! More!
More!
More, babe! More, babe!
Nice one, babe!
Let’s do another cheers!
Cheers!
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
I’m done! I’m done—
Ari?
Yes?
Shhh... Keep quiet. You’re Ari, right?
Sorry—What is it?
Hi, I’m Janna.
What do you need?
Your boyfriend, Tristan,
he’s outside the center.
He said he wants to see you.
Huh?
You’re able to go out?
Shhh! Don’t be loud!
I know a way out of here.
Come with me, he
really wants to see you.
Ah...
Isn’t what you’re doing forbidden?
Duh—Of course it is.
But I think I’d go crazy if I stayed here.
Look, if you don’t want to,
I’ll just go and tell him
you’re not interested.
Uh—wait, wait...
We really won’t get caught?
Ari, I sneak out every night.
I’ve never been caught.
Okay, fine, fine.
Tonight, okay?
I’ll come back for you.
Is it still far?
Janna, are you sure
this is the right way?
Just follow me.
Tristan?
Hi, babe.
How are you?
I’m okay...
I’ll go take a walk for a bit.
Thanks!
Babe, let’s sit.
Come here.
Hi...
You really drove all the way here?
Yeah, is it that hard to believe?
It’s not that. It’s just... it’s really late.
Actually, babe, I’ve been here
since this afternoon.
I saw you there, at the balcony.
No way. Seriously?
I just took a chance I might see you,
since I know visitors aren’t allowed.
Then why are you still here?
I didn’t want to go home earlier.
I really felt like I’d see
you and talk to you.
See? Was I wrong?
I missed you so much.
I missed you too, babe.
It hasn’t even been a week,
but I already miss you so much.
I love you.
I love you, too, baby.
Oh, sorry! I didn’t mean to interrupt,
but we need to go back.
They’re about to wake up.
Alright, alright.
-Let’s see each other again?
-Of course, babe.
See you soon, okay?
Let’s go.
Thank you.
Ari, can I talk to you in my office?
I’ll wait for you there.
-How are you—
-Uhm...
I’m okay.
That’s good.
I hope...
all is really well during
your first week here.
So, since you arrived here,
has anything memorable happened?
Aah...
Not really.
Alright...
Maybe you can just tell
me about your day,
what usually happens, like
from the time you wake up
until you go to bed. Something like that?
Aah...
I’m still adjusting my sleep.
So sometimes when I
wake up, it feels like
I didn’t get enough sleep.
But of course, I still have to get up,
so after I eat,
I just hang out outside.
I look at the trees.
Next thing I know,
it’s night again. Then...
I just try to fall asleep.
Pretty boring, huh?
Very.
But you know, that’s totally normal.
Because you were removed from
your normal life, or at least the
life you were used to.
So it’s hard to adjust.
But it’s part of the process.
You mentioned having
trouble sleeping,
is there a reason for that?
Last night...
I had a dream.
Huh? What was it about?
I saw the things we used to do.
When I was totally wasted,
and when my best friend and I used,
along with my boyfriend.
But you know what,
I kept saying in my dream
that I didn’t want it anymore.
We’ve had many cases like that.
And... it’s valid.
What I like about what
you said is that
you acknowledged you
don’t want it anymore.
That is two steps going forward.
You are trying to heal
and it’s clear to you
that you want out.
I hope this continues, okay?
You just take your medicines regularly
and follow the rules here,
for your healing.
Because when you leave the center
and go back on your own,
it’s up to you
whether you continue to live a better life,
or allow yourself to go back
to your old ways.
So...
while you’re here,
I suggest you try to have
new habits,
try a new lifestyle,
make new friends!
Okay?
Okay.
Ari.
Hey, you've been ignoring
me since last night.
It’s nothing…
-I saw you last night--
-Hey! Someone might hear you.
Do you see something I don’t?
OMG! Is that why you’re here?
Silly.
Don’t be shy.
It’s just me. And that’s normal, okay?
You missed each other, that’s all.
So what exactly did you see?
A full-length movie. That kind.
Gosh--
It’s Tristan--
Just to be clear, I’m not always like that.
There’s nothing wrong with it.
Come on.
And you know what?
That was my first time outdoors.
Oh no, you’re missing out!
Go on, explore.
Try all sorts of things.
Try something new.
But why didn’t you say anything?
And you won’t get to finish?
Besides...
I actually enjoyed watching you.
Why do you seem so okay with it
like you’re used to seeing that stuff?
Well, in case you didn’t know,
that’s the reason my ex-boyfriend
had me admitted here.
Ex-fiancé, to be exact.
Huh? Why?
He said I had a sex addiction.
“He said,” okay?
I think he just brought me here
as a way to get out
of our relationship.
Maybe he just couldn’t keep up
with my energy in bed
and everywhere else.
So I gave it to him.
I broke up with him.
After all, he already paid for this rehab.
So how often did you
ask for it to be called
an “addict”?
Hmmm... once, sometimes twice,
or thrice.
Isn’t that normal though?
Three times a day?
That’s “normal”?
Yes! Especially on
special occasions.
So, how about you?
Why are you here?
I’ve seen you around for a week now,
but you looked kind of grumpy.
Maybe you’re a snob,
so I didn’t bother trying.
I’m not. But...
my case is alcohol and drug addiction.
Oh! So you’re the real addict here.
See? You’re so grumpy.
I was only teasing you.
You know, what we’re going
through is far from ideal,
so let’s make it fun, right?
You’re right.
Same time tonight?
Sure.
I have a feeling
Tristan’s coming back.
For sure! Especially after your
performance last night.
Tan!
Hey, come out of there.
Tristan!
Keep your voice down,
someone might hear us.
He’s not here.
This is where I saw him last night.
He wouldn’t be traveling this late, right?
Maybe he’s just running late?
Did he tell you
he was coming today?
Yeah, he said we’d
see each other again.
Maybe something came up,
an emergency or something.
There are still more nights,
more chances.
Or maybe he already got
what he wanted last night
and didn’t feel the
need to come back.
What do you want, anyway?
Nothing.
Come on, you wanted
round two, didn’t you?
No, I didn’t.
Come with me. Let’s go somewhere.
-Where? Where are we going?
-Just come. Just trust me.
Where are we, Janna?
Feels like we’ve gone far.
-Isn’t this dangerous? It’s late--
-Come on! Let’s have fun!
--Let’s sit here at the sides.
-Let’s go back--
-They might be looking for us--
-It’s beautiful here!
We won’t get caught here, right?
It really feels better when
you’re not doing this alone.
‘Cause when I sneak out,
I feel like I’m going crazy,
doing this all by myself.
Good thing you’re here.
Good thing you talked to me.
Thank you too, Janna.
You know what I said earlier,
that you should explore more,
that you should try new things.
Janna, come on! Hurry!
Someone might spot us any moment.
Wait, wait--
-Don’t panic...
-It’s just that--
I always sneak out at
this time of night.
I’ve never been caught here before.
-What if we get caught. Come on, hurry!
-It’s okay.
Ari?
What happened?
We just talked yesterday, right?
Maám, I’m sorry.
Ari, I’m going to put this on record.
Same with you, Janna.
And this might affect your stay here.
We might have to recommend
an extension for both of you.
Because you may need additional
sessions and medications.
Ma’am, please...
Could you please let it go this time?
Ma’am, it’s my fault.
I just pulled Ari with me to go outside.
I just wanted someone to be with.
-It’s not her fault.
-Janna...
Ari, it’s your last week here.
So I hope you make the
most of it to heal
and open up to me so I can help you.
And you, Janna,
I hope this will be the
last time this happens.
You need to make time to talk to me
so I can help you.
You need it.
I promise.
Janna,
why’d you do that?
Hey, you’re being too serious.
Come on, it’s nothing.
It’s fine.
But what’s going to
happen to you now?
Ari, what are you even scared of?
That I might get extended here?
That’s even better.
I don’t really have anything
waiting for me outside.
No one’s out there for me.
It’s better here. It’s more peaceful.
And you don’t have to
Think about anything.
See?
So don’t worry about it anymore.
Thank you, Janna.
Don’t mention it.
Let’s hear from Ari.
I slept well last night,
so when I woke up,
-it felt so good.
-Really refreshed.
Yes! And...
I’ve really been savoring
the cold water lately.
Everything feels like a blessing to me.
Happy graduation!
Hey, take care, okay?
You too.
Try not to sneak out
too often, alright?
Yes, ma’am!
If you say so.
-I’m going to miss you.
-I’ll wait for you...
I’ll wait for you out there, okay?
Of course. I’ll come find you.
I’m going to miss you.
I’ll miss you too.
Knock knock.
Ready to go, Ari?
Yes, ma’am.
Let me help you.
Ari, sweetheart, come eat now.
Sorry, I kind of moved
some stuff in your room.
I cleaned it up while you were gone.
I also followed the instructions
to remove everything that could
trigger your relapse.
Thank you, Ma.
Ari... I hope you're doing better now.
I hope you understand why we
brought you there.
It was for your own good.
I hope you won’t resent us for it.
It’s okay, Ma.
And lastly...
I know it won't go away just like that,
because you’ve only been in rehab
for two weeks.
But please, Ari. Try your best.
Welcome back.
-Eat up.
-Your cooking’s really the best, Ma.
What are you doing here?
I came to see you.
How did you know I was back?
I went to the center. I saw Janna and she said
you were already home.
Babe...
You didn’t come see me after the night
we saw each other.
Baby, I’m sorry. I just had an emergency.
My car broke down so I couldn’t make it.
But I still went the next
day just to see you.
Really?
Yeah, I promise.
But then you and Janna weren’t there.
I was hoping you’d be there
the next night, but no luck.
-We got caught sneaking out.
-Yeah, Janna told me about that.
Baby, you know I love you, right?
You know that, right?
I’d do anything just to see you.
I’m sorry... I just really missed you.
Babe, I missed you too. At least now
we can spend more time together.
I love you.
-Babe?
-Hmm?
Portia found out you're back.
Uh... It’s her birthday tomorrow.
She said she’s throwing a party.
Wanna come?
I don’t feel like going, babe.
Even just to drop by? Just greet her.
You know you never missed your
best friend’s birthday.
So? You okay, babe?
We’ll just stay for a bit, okay?
Besides, it’s a chance for me
to make it up to her too.
Alright.
Right? And what she said was so funny--
Right? I told you--
-What’s up? What’s up? What’s up?
-Hey!
-Hi, babe!
-Come on. Come on, have some good shit--
-What’s this?
-Come on, I got you.
-Babe, I’ll be back.
-No, stay here...
Babe, just for a bit.
I’ll be right back, I promise.
Hey, babe...
How are you? How have you been?
I’m okay... Happy birthday!
-What?
-Happy birthday!
Thank you. Thank you! You know,
I’m so glad you’re here.
Of course, it’s you!
But I’m only staying a bit, okay?
-Why?
-It’s just...
-I just really wanted to drop by.
-Okay. Whatever.
As long as you’re here, I’m so happy--
I’m so happy, babe!
Come on, I’ll introduce you to my
other friends. Come on, come here.
Wait-- let me just grab something quick.
Take a seat, and I’ll be right there, okay?
-Okay--
-I’ll see you, babe...
Thank you-- Thank you!
Ah, thank you...
Ma...
What happened to what we talked about?
Didn’t I tell you to stop seeing Tristan?
What else needs to happen to you?
Ari, please... Stop...
Help yourself.
That’s enough too, Ma...
Just send me back to rehab
so you won’t have to deal with me anymore.
So I won’t be a burden anymore.
I’m sorry, Ma...
I messed up.
-Babe.
-Hey, babe. What’s wrong? How are you?
My mom found out what
happened last night.
I shouldn’t have gone there in the first place.
Babe, I’m sorry. What happened?
-I’m going back to the center.
-What? Again?
I need to take this seriously.
You should too.
We need to fix this.
Babe, I don’t understand.
I was thinking, come with me.
Let’s both check into the center.
Huh? Why?
Babe, for this relationship to work,
we both need to fix ourselves.
This isn’t just for us. It’s also so you
can be okay with my mom.
She wants me to break up with you.
But please, let’s prove her wrong.
Come with me.
If you really love me,
you’ll come with me.
Babe, can’t we just share a room?
You’re crazy, babe.
Of course not.
What matters is we’re here together.
Thank you for coming with me.
Ari! OMG, you’re back!
I missed you.
I missed you too.
You too?
Ari convinced me.
Why? What happened?
Aside from missing the calmness
and the quiet of rehab,
I had a relapse.
You left so quickly last time.
That wouldn’t have helped much.
Exactly, so here I am again.
I don’t know how long this time.
I brought Tristan with me.
Is he the one who’s a
bad influence on you?
Hey! It’s not me.
You know, you’re both the same.
Both of you love to deny things.
Since you called me a bad influence...
I’ll be a bad influence on both of you.
Huh?
Let’s sneak out.
Let’s show Tristan how we do it.
-Janna.
-I’m in.
He’s in. Let’s go.
You know, Ari,
since there’s nothing you’re
looking forward to after rehab
and in case your sanction gets extended,
why not?
This is the last time.
I promise, we won’t get caught.
-Okay, fine.
-Okay.
You know, I’m really glad you’re here.
I have someone with me again.
Of course. But didn’t you say,
this is the last time?
Well,
I don’t have anyone to secretly
meet outside anymore.
Tristan’s already here, and so are you.
You don’t have to sneak out anymore.
-Nice, right?
-Ugh, here comes the sermon again.
But you know what,
when you were gone,
I really struggled.
Shh, come on.
You don’t have to think
about that anymore.
I’m here now.
And it’s not just me--
Tristan’s here too.
See? We gained one more.
I’m glad you chose to come back
after what happened.
It’s for the better.
Good thing you brought Tristan too.
I knew he needed help too.
Thank you for convincing him.
I hope you can
convince Janna too.
She still won’t talk?
Not yet.
But maybe you...
Maybe you can convince her
so we can help her.
Babe,
have you seen Janna?
No. She’s been gone for a while.
Janna!
Babe.
What happened?
I went to the clinic earlier.
Huh? How--
Because if it’s from the other night--
it wouldn’t show up this fast.
Did you sleep with someone else
before we came here?
Hey!
Hey, what’s happening?
Tristan, do you know anything about this?
You two saw each other--
while I was gone?
Don’t tell me something happened
between you two?
Sorry, Ari.
It’s my fault.
-What the hell, Janna!
-Please, stop.
Why Tristan too? Why?
Please stop. I’m sorry.
Sorry? Sorry?
Well guess what?
Something happened between me
and Janna too.
So that’s why the other night
you were enjoying it so much.
When she kissed you,
you didn’t even flinch.
Well, shit. Look what happened.
You got her pregnant.
And you...
Babe, stop, please.
You-- I trusted you.
You were my friend.
Why did it have to be us?
We let you fool us.
You know what?
Your ex was right.
You need help,
instead of treating this place
as a vacation stay.
What are you going to do now?
What’s your plan?
Let go of me.
Janna!
Tristan...
He ran away.
Took all his stuff with him.
What an asshole. All he knows
is how to enjoy life.
That coward.
I should’ve just listened to my mom.
This is my fault.
If it weren’t for me
you two wouldn’t have met.
Then none of this would’ve happened.
Come on, Ari. It’s not your fault.
This was my choice.
I’ll fix this.
Finally!
So, what do you want to talk about?
I’m an addict.
I’m addicted to sex.
Thank you for
acknowledging that, Janna.
May I ask you something?
What do you feel
when you have sex?
It feels good.
You keep craving that feeling.
But on a deeper level...
Why do you think that is?
What does it give you?
Maybe that’s the only time
I feel like I’m not alone.
Because I grew up on my own.
Ever since I discovered sex,
it’s like that’s when I finally felt
a real connection.
Like there were people out there for me.
So I kept looking for it.
Because I don’t want to
feel alone anymore.
I heard you’re having a baby, Janna?
Yes, well...
It was unexpected…
I had sex.
Janna, your life is different now.
You now have someone--
someone to be with.
I hope you find new priorities
in your life,
or a new purpose.
I know it’s not just yourself
you’ll be thinking of anymore.
You have to know your priorities.
I suggest you slowly shift your focus
on the baby
and make sure you take care
of him or her.
This is only the beginning, Janna.
I know you’ll get better.